Guide to the James Perkins papers,1963-1969.
Perkins, James papers,1963-1969.
- Series III. 1967-1969
  - Cornell University Airplane., 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - University Faculty., 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 44-45)
  - University Faculty Meetings, Agendas., 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 46-48)
  - University Faculty Minutes., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
  - University Faculty Committees., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - University Faculty Council., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
  - University Lectures., 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder S)
  - Prizes., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Student Conduct., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs., 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Lattin, George W.; Pimentel, David. Faculty Committee on Student Affairs on the Present Adjudicative System and Defects Alleged by Afro-American Society, report.
  - Calendar., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Music., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Economic Status of the Faculty., 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Necrology., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
  - Academic Freedom and Tenure., 1969 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Salaries of Faculty and Assistants., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Kurd, T. Norman.
  - Endowed Professorships., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Leussink, Ing. Hans; Schwartz, Richard J.; LaFeber, Walter F. Krupp Foundation; Henry Luce Foundation, Inc.; Carl Marks Professorship in International Studies; John S. Knight Professorship in International Studies; Nicholas H. Noyes Professorship; Jacob Gould Schurman Professorship; Schwartz Professorship in the Social Studies; Marie Underhill Noll Chair in American History.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    LaMont, Thomas E.; Adams, Morton.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
    Palm, Charles E. Committee: The New York State College of Agriculture and the Next Quarter Century.
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Departments. Brady, Nyle C., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Bradfield and Emerson Halls Dedication., 1968 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Emerson, Sterling; Purcell, Robert W.; Saltonstall, Leverett.
  - Laboratory of Ornithology., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    O'Jones, Smith Q.
  - Geneva Experiment Station. Barton, Donald W. Parrott Hall., 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - College of Architecture., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    Kelly, Burnham; Ungers, Oswald Mathias. National Accrediting Board, Inc.
  - College of Architecture., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    Kelly, Burnham; Parsons, Kermit C.; Cohen, Henry. Richard King Mellon Charitable Trusts.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    Williams, L. Pearce; Kagan, Donald; Brown, Stuart M.; Hirshfeld, Barbara B. Minorities.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    Brown, Stuart M.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Slatoff, Walter J.; McPhelin, Michael; Sindler, Allan P. Racism; Black students.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    Brown, Stuart M.; Burak, David; Parrish, Stephen M. Ithaca Festival; Admissions.
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    Parrish, Stephen M.; Ascher, Robert; Philbrick, Shailer S.; Myrdal, Gunnar; Sindler, Allan P. Society for the Humanities; University Committee on Anthropology; Six Year Ph.D. Program.
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    Parrish, Stephen M.; Sindler, Allan P.; Rossiter, Clinton. NASA; Ford Foundation; Metropolitan Museum Professorship; Six Year Ph.D. Program; Cornell University Center for Radiophysics and Space Research.
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    Strout, Gushing; Webb, James E.; Gold, Thomas; Kahin, George McT. NASA; Space Sciences Building; Theatre Arts Dept.
  - College of Arts and Sciences Departments., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    Sindler, Allan P.; Sharp, Lauriston; Harding, H.F. Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory; Rhetoric and Public Speaking Program; Dept. of Government report.
  - Chemistry., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    Gurowitz, William D.; Queeny, Edgar M.; Hoffman, Roald. National Science Foundation; Monsanto Chemical Company; Baker Laboratory.
  - Chemistry., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    Carpenter, Walter S. National Science Foundation.
  - Economics., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    Bickel, Gary W.; McPhelin, Michael; Brown, Stuart M.; Nerlove, Marc; Davis, Thomas E.; Morse, Chandler. Rockefeller Foundation; Center for Quantitative Research in Economics and Business.
  - Far Eastern Studies., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    Kahin, George McT.
  - History., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    Potts, John F.; Marcham, Frederick G.
  - Mathematics., 1968 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Computing Center., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Modern Languages., 1968 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    Sola, Donald F. Inter-American Linguistic Institute.
  - Music., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Band., 1968 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Sage Chapel Choir., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Romance Literature., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    Parrish, Jean; Demorest, Jean-Jacques.
  - Psychology., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    Levin, Harry. Kenan Professorship.
  - Sociology and Anthropology., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    Stycos, Jose Mayone. International Population Program; Population Reference Bureau; Conference on Human Mobility.
  - Center for Environmental Quality Management., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Center for International Studies., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    Ashford, Douglas E.; Lowenstein, Allard K.; Esman, Milton. Ford Foundation; Symposium on Southern Africa.
  - Center for International Studies., 1967-69 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    Ashford, Douglas E.; Smock, David R. Students for A Democratic Society (SDS); Symposium on Southern Africa; Ford Foundation.
  - Center for International Studies., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    Kahn, Alfred E.; Ashford, Douglas E.; Einaudi, Mario. South Africa.
  - Center for International Studies., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    Ashford, Douglas E.; Einaudi, Mario; Liu, Ta-Chung; Long, Franklin A.
  - Center for International Studies., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    Einaudi, Mario; Ashford, Douglas E.; Moore, Richard V. International Education Act Regional Conference.
  - College of Engineering., 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    Schultz, Andrew. Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory; College of Engineering faculty.
  - Civil Engineering., 1968 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Electrical Engineering., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - New York State College of Home Economics. Knapp, David C. College of Home Economics faculty; Name change; Revision to University Charter., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - New York State College of Home Economics. Knapp, David C. College of Home Economics faculty., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - New York State College of Home Economics. Knapp, David C.; Miller, Mary Rogers; Canoyer, Helen G. College of Home Economics faculty., 1967-69 (Box 26, Folder 3-5)
  - New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Corson, Dale R. Name change., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Blackwell Report; Name change.
  - New York State Veterinary College., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Poppensiek, George C. Willard Straight Hall occupation.
  - New York State Veterinary College., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Poppensiek, George C. American Veterinary Medicine Association
  - New York State Veterinary College., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Poppensiek, George C. American Veterinary Medicine Association Cornell-San Marcos Intercollege Program.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Luckey, E. Hugh; Deitrick, John E.; Barzun, Jacques.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Luckey, E. Hugh; Hinsey, Joseph C.; Lillehei, C. Walton.
  - Cornell: University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Hinsey, Joseph C.; Bundy, McGeorge. Minorities.
  - Cornell; University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Hinsey, Joseph C.; Deitrick, John E.
  - Cornell; University Medical College and New York Hospital, Executive Faculty Minutes., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 15-18)
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital Finances., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital Joint Administrative Board., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 20-21)
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 22-23)
  - Law School., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    Heath, Frank C.; Forrester, Ray; Anthony, Robert A. Cornell Law Association; Cornell Law Forum.
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Moore, David G. Civil rights; Black Studies Program; Faculty., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    Moore, David G.; Corson, Dale R. Cornell-Turin International Centre Program.
  - School of Nursing., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    McGuire, Joseph W.; Davidson, H. Justin; Trued, Merlyn N.; Thomas, David A. Deanship.
  - School of Hotel Administration., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    Beck, Robert A.; Meek, Howard B.
  - Statler Club., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - School of Education., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Graduate School of Nutrition., 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Barnes, Richard H.
  - Graduate School., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    Cooke, W. Donald. Human Rights Commission; Commission on Teaching Assistants.
  - Graduate School., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    Cooke, W. Donald; Leurgans, Paul J. United States Selective Service.
  - Graduate School., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    Cooke, W. Donald. United States Selective Service.
  - Division of Unclassified Students., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Division of Biological Sciences., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Military Science and Tactics, ROTC., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Air ROTC., 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    Kennedy, William E.
  - Physical Education and Athletics., 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    Kane, Robert J.; McGuinn, Robert.
  - Women's Sports., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Confidential Letters (Kane, Mimeo)., 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ivy League., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    [Out to Mark Barlow, 30 Sep 1969.]
  - Naval ROTC., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Prince, Mortimer F.; Reynolds, F.G.
  - Newman Laboratory., 1968 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    McDaniel, Boyce. D.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session., 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Social Science Research Center., 1965 (Box 27, Folder S)
  - Cornell Plantations., 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Lewis, Richard M.
  - University Health Services, Infirmary and Clinic., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Beck, Frederick.
  - CURW., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Berrigan, Daniel; Cole, Ned; Konvitz, Milton R.; Barlow, Mark; Lewis, W. Jack; Sokol, Thomas A. Sage Chapel services; Visiting evaluation.
  - CURW. Berrigan, Daniel; Barlow, Mark; Lewis, W. Jack. Sage Chapel., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - CURW., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Berrigan, Daniel; Barlow, Mark.
  - CURW., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Danforth Foundation., 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Danforth Fellowship.
  - Alumni Office., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 16-19)
    Clifford, Frank R.; Bradley, Hunt; Hall, Jackson 0.
  - Cornell Clubs., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Alumni News. Joseph, Gloria I.; Newsom, Barbara; Marcham, John. Black students., 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Scholarships, Grants, Gifts., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    Rockefeller, Laurance S.; Purcell, Robert W.
  - Scholarships, Grants, Gifts., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 23-24)
  - Cornell National Scholarships., 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - SUNY., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    Gould, Samuel B.
  - SUNY., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    Campus Academic Plan; Campus Development Plan.
  - SUNY., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    Gould, Samuel B.; Morse, F.A. Master Plan for SUNY.
  - SUNY., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 29-30)
    Development Plan for SUNY.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - New York State Education Dept. Nyquist, Ewald B.; Alien, James E.; Kille, Frank R., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - New York State Education Dept., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    Nyquist, Ewald B. Five College Project.
  - New York State Education Dept. Alien, James E.; Conant, James B.; Kuusisto, Allan A. Master Plan., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - New York State Education Dept., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    Financial aid.
  - Regents. Morse, F.A. Press releases., 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - A Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    African-American Institute.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    Anderson, Robert 0.; Ashby, Eric.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    Aspinall, Francis H. Associated Universities, Inc.
  - American Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    Golay, Frank H. American Academy of Arts and Sciences; American Association of University Professors; Academic freedom.
  - American Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    Golay, Frank H. American Association of University Professors; American Civil Liberties Union; Academic freedom.
  - American Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    American Council of Learned Societies.
  - American Council on Education., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 43-46)
  - Applicants for Jobs., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Association Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Association of American Colleges., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
    Sullivan, Richard H.
  - Association of American Universities., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 6-8)
  - B-BN Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Bache, Alice K.; Balzer, Richard; Barradas, Gerald.
  - B-BN Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - B-BN Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Berns, Walter F.; Bethe, Rose; Ngere, L.O. Biafra.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Bolgiano, Ralph; Bozzoli, G.R.; Brady, Nyle C.; Brewster, Kingman.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Browne, Robert S. The Bridge, A Center for the Advancement of Intercultural Studies; Black students.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Bundy, McGeorge; Burak, David.
  - BOCES., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    University of California.
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1967-`969 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Challenge Industries, Inc.; Chase Manhattan Bank.
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Chess, Stanley D.; Chublarian, Rouben.
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Closson, B. Michael.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    Collier, Leonard H. College Entrance Examination Board.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Columbia University.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    Coors, Joseph. Cornell Day; Cornell in Perspective.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Clark, Van Alan., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    Clark, Edna. Edna McConnell Clark Foundation.
  - Council on Creative and Performing Arts. Ammons, Archie R., 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Alumni Committee for Balanced Education. Tuller, J. Daniel; Hawes, Marshall., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Cornell conference., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Convocation., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 28-29)
  - Cornell Research Park., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Carpenter, Walter S., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Condolences., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Conferences., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 33-34)
  - Committee on Conferences., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Congressional and New York State Bills., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 36-38)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education, Inc., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    Davis, David B.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    Day, Harold C.; Demorest, Jean- Jacques.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    Diamant, Sarah Elbert; Dixon, Phelan; Djilas, Milovan.
  - D Miscellaneous Dowd, Douglas F. Dow Chemical Company., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Dancis, Bruce D., 1968-69 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    Draft card destruction.
  - Disadvantaged Students., 1964-68 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    President's Committee on Disadvantaged, Students; A Program of Corporate-University Cooperation.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    Eaton, Cyrus; Eden, Anthony; Kahin, George McT.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    Edwards, Harry; Egler, Frank E.; Eilenberg, Larry. EDUCOM.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    Einaudi, Mario; Epstein, Mark; Epstein, Albert.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    Esman, Milton.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    Fiedler, Elliott.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - F Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    Frank, Konstantin; Freeman, Harrop A.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Fifteen Universities., 1967-68 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - French Higher Education., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Morris, Edward.
  - Ford Foundation - Present Danger., 1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 6 Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Gardner, John W.
  - 6 Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Gemmell, Edgar M.; Glennan, T. Keith; Golay, Frank H.; Goldschlager, Seth S.
  - 6 Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Gomberg, William; Grasselli, Caesar A.; Gross, James A.; Guerlac, Henry.
  - General Electric Company., 1968-69 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Daniel and Florence Guggenheim Foundation., 1963-68 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - H-HN Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Hacker, Andrew; Hall, Robert A.; Hamilton, Thomas J. CURW: Sage Chapel; New York Times.
  - H-HN Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Hatchett, John F.; Henning, Dyle G.
  - HO-HZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Holley, Robert W. Humanities Council.
  - I Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    International Association of University Presidents.
  - I Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    International Christian University; Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants.
  - I Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Irwin, Paul C.; Goldman, Jack. Ithaca Neighborhood Center; Ithaca Neighborhood College.
  - Inaugurations, Ceremonies, Dedications., 1968-69 (Box 29, Folder 15-17)
  - Inaugurations., 1967-68 (Box 29, Folder 18-21)
  - Institute Miscellaneous., 1968 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - International Association of Universities., 1968-69 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Invitations - Ithaca., 1967-68 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Invitations - Out of Town., 1967-68 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Invitations Declined., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 26-30)
  - Center for the Arts at Ithaca., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 31-32)
  - J Miscellaneous., 1968-69 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    Javits, Jacob K.; Joseph, Gloria I. Johnson Foundation; COSEP.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    Kagan, Donald; Kahin, George McT.; Kaminsky, Arthur C.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    Corson, Dale R.; Levin, Harry; Kennedy, Robert F.; Kerr, Clark. Kenan Chair; William R. Kenan Charitable Trust.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    Kettering, Eugene W.; Keyes, Alan.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    Konvitz, Milton R.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    Leussink, Ing. Hans.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    Linowitz, Sol M. London-Cornel1 Project.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    London-Cornell Project.
  - Henry Luce Foundation, Inc., 1968-69 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    Henry R. Luce Professorship of Science and Society.
  - MA-MN Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - MA-MN Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    McMaster, Donald.
  - MA-MN Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    Miller, Paul. Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools.
  - MA-MN Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    Mizener, Arthur M.
  - MO-MZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Morey, Robert H.; Morris, Evan J. Mohawk Airlines; Tompkins County Airport.
  - MO-MZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Morse, Chandler; Murphy, Royse P.; Muskie, Edmund S.; Myrdal, Gunnar.
  - Morison Commission ("Future of Student Organization11)., 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
    Morison, Robert S.; MacNeil, Ian.
  - MOVE., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Parker, Reeve; Purcell, Robert W.; Kotelchuck, Ronda. Students for a Democratic Society (SDS); Housing.
  - N Miscellaneous*, 1967-69. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Nelson, Gaylord; Nerlove, Marc. Student protest.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Bragdon, Paul E. New York Civil Liberties Union; New York College Bound Corporation; Student protest.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder S)
    Nikolayew, Irene; Noll, Marie Underhill. University of Notre Dame.
  - National Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    NASA; National Collegiate Athletic Association; National Institute of Health; National Research Council; National Endowment for the Humanities.
  - National Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    National Industrial Conference Board; National Youth Conference on Civic Affairs.
  - National Assn. of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 11-15)
  - New York State Legislature, Bundy Plan., 1969 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - New York State., 1967-68 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    New York State Dormitory Authority.
  - New York State., 1967-68 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Constitutional Convention., 1967 (Box 30, Folder 19-21)
  - Newman, Floyd R., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    Mackesey, Thomas W. Cornell Plantations; Arboretum.
  - Noyes, Jansen Sr., 1967-68 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - O Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    Orear, Jay.
  - PA-PK Miscellaneous., 1967-69. (Box 30, Folder 25)
    Papish, Jacob. Peace Corps.
  - PA-PK Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    Pierce, Nathaniel W. Joseph Newton Pew Jr. Professorship.
  - PL-PZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    Princeton University; Students for a Democratic Society (SDS); Selective Service; Student protest.
  - President's Meeting, Campus Stability, 26 June 1968, New York City., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Q Miscellaneous., 1967-68 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    Quill and Dagger Society.
  - Questionnaires., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - RA-RK Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    Rathjens, George W.; Requardt, Gustav J.
  - RA-RK Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - RL-RZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    Rockefeller, David; Rockefeller, Laurance S.; Rockwell, Mary.
  - RL-RZ Miscellaneous., 1967-69 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    Rogers, William P.; Romulo, Carlos P.